<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<data>
	<TIPLIST>
		<TIP>A live opponent has not arrived yet. You may continue waiting or hit Stop to exit matchmaking.</TIP>
		<TIP>If you're experiencing performance issues, you can toggle special effects on and off from the options. This may help!</TIP>
		<TIP>You can rename your commander units by inspecting them in the commanders list.</TIP>
		<TIP>Having trouble finding a live match? Try starting a few untimed (play-by-mail) multiplayer matches instead. You can play several simultaneously!</TIP>
		<TIP>If you have more than 2 of a given unit, you can trade up the extras for new ones from the crafting screen! Just click the hammer button in the deck editor.</TIP>
		<TIP>For every 4 attack power your army generates, above your opponent's attack power, you will deal 1 additional damage to the enemy city!</TIP>
		<TIP>Drag a wounded unit over your city or the recruit bar to disband it and receive half of its value back.</TIP>
		<TIP>Visit our web forums for updates on the game and to share strategy tips with other players!</TIP>
		<TIP>There are audio quick-keys: Press 0 to toggle sound on and off, and press + and - to adjust the volume.</TIP>
		<TIP>There are three different animation speed settings accessible from the options menu: SLOW, FAST, and MAX. Switch to MAX if you want battles to progress very quickly.</TIP>
		<TIP>There are over 200 unique units in Highgrounds!</TIP>
		<TIP>Live matches pit you against the first available opponent to minimize wait times. If you'd like to ensure more balanced encounters, try playing some untimed matches.</TIP>
		<TIP>You can challenge players on the leaderboard who have a skill rating close to yours!</TIP>
		<TIP>Defending against multi-wound is an important skill to learn! Try staggering your front row with a couple of strong defensive units. A unit with 3 or 4 defense can absorb most heavy wound!</TIP>
		<TIP>Juggle your units! If you always leave them in the same place, your opponent will have an easy time wounding you and landing big blows. Try to keep them guessing.</TIP>
		<TIP>More useful and rare Types are offered as upgrade options the higher your Commander rises in level.</TIP>
		<TIP>You can unlock additional commander units by leveling up your commanders. New slots open up when the previous commander reaches 70% of their max level.</TIP>
		<TIP>Be sure to finish the single player campaign! It awards a number of free units that can greatly improve your starter deck.</TIP>
		<TIP>Daily and Weekly events reset at 11:59PM GMT.</TIP>
		<TIP>Find more tips and tricks from other players on our forums at heartshapedgames.com</TIP>
		<TIP>You can change the city for your deck in the deck editor. Everyone gets all 10 unique cities!</TIP>
		<TIP>Check the Quests menu for goals and achievements that earn you free gems and units.</TIP>
		<TIP>Forest faction units are often weak to Wound.</TIP>
		<TIP>The shop features a new individual unit for sale each day. A great way to grab units that have alluded you in booster packs.</TIP>
		<TIP>Wound and Arrow can be blocked by defense.</TIP>
		<TIP>Smaller decks can be less random and give more chances of drawing the unit you need.</TIP>
		<TIP>In the first turn, it's generally a good idea to focus on collecting resources instead of damage.</TIP>
		<TIP>Your first hand of a battle will always contain a unit you can hire.</TIP>
		<TIP>Don't like your Commander's abilities? You can respec them for a small cost via the base camp commander menu.</TIP>
		<TIP>If you enjoy the game, help us spread the word! Heart Shaped Games is a small developer, and word of mouth recommendations go a long way!</TIP>
		<TIP>There are filters in the bottom right corner of the deck editor that let you sort your collection by faction.</TIP>
		<TIP>Playing on a game portal? Consider giving us a 5-Star rating on your favorite site!</TIP>
		<TIP>It's a good idea to heal wounded units ahead of when they take their turn.</TIP>
		<TIP>Try to protect your healers by shifting their position or surrounding them with defenders.</TIP>
		<TIP>Turns are simultaneous in Highgrounds. Both players lock in their moves, then see the results play out.</TIP>
	</TIPLIST>
</data>